{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian9.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "Anche i miei cugini sono un po' stressati.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1453400441.7501929,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My cousins are a little stressed, too.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "La sua automobile e' rossa.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1453400533.7114666,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"His car is red.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "il nostro letto",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1453400358.8260214,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"our bed\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "il tuo appartmento",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1453400373.11156,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"your apartment\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il mio giardino, invece, e' molto piccolo.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1453400416.757359,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My garden, on the other hand, is very small.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "I tuoi piatti sono gialli.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400343.465845,
            "question": "Your dishes are yellow.",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Le nostre lavatrici sono bianche.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1453400546.6062925,
            "question": "Our washing machines are white.",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "La sua cucina e' bella.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400319.371104,
            "question": "Her kitchen is beautiful.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "vostre",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400737.0721686,
            "question": "y'alls (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il suo tavolo e' grande.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400730.2280588,
            "question": "His/Her table is big.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "I tuoi cuscini sono verdi.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400838.1797106,
            "question": "Your pillows are green.",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "tue",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400840.9961784,
            "question": "your (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mia madre, Laura, e' un po' stressata.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400713.5209887,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My mother, Laura is a little stressed.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "la sua bicicletta",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400565.1885674,
            "question": "Given the definition \"her bike\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "suo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400571.220133,
            "question": "his, her (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "I miei nonni sono felici.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400824.053975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My grandparents are happy.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "il vostro cuscino",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400874.8451304,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"y'alls pillow\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mia cugina e' simpatica.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400948.3560336,
            "question": "Tua cucina e' simpatica. (mia)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "la sua automobile",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400854.6687677,
            "question": "Given the definition \"his car\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "La tua mamma e' dolce.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1453400924.9017496,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Your mom is sweet.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "nostra",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400955.418903,
            "question": "our (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "il suo tavolo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400964.6731079,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"his/her table\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il vostro divano e' rosso.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453400907.0852451,
            "question": "Y'alls couch is red.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "invece",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1453400951.5749238,
            "question": "Given the definition \"instead\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "vostro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401023.437558,
            "question": "y'alls (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "La mia casa e' vecchia.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401064.6111958,
            "question": "My house is old.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401054.7546844,
            "question": "their (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "y'alls pillow",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401048.2231114,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il vostro cuscino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "tuo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401017.3403146,
            "question": "your (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "suoi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453400976.7987385,
            "question": "Il suo bambino e' in giardino. -> I ___ bambini sono in giardino.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mia sorella, Ann, e' molto intelligente.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401011.8556535,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My sister, Ann, is very intelligent.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "tuoi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453400991.1075065,
            "question": "Tuo zio e' in camera da letto. -> I ___ zii sono in camera da letto.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "il loro tappeto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1453401300.0757577,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"their rug\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "La sua bicicletta e' verde.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1453401314.602881,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Her bike is green.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "a little",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401116.777014,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un po'\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Their apartments are old.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401268.766694,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I loro appartamenti sono vecchi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401072.1428459,
            "question": "La loro casa e' grande. Le ___ case sono grandi.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sua madre e' dolce.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401085.365214,
            "question": "Vostra madre e' dolce. (sua)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "his car",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401113.76123,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la sua automobile\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I loro appartamenti sono vecchi.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401292.506227,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Their apartments are old.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "nere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401391.3511379,
            "question": "Le pentole sono ner_",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "un po'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401326.497102,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a little\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "nostro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401340.404075,
            "question": "our (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401329.96603,
            "question": "their (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "nostri",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401394.8513196,
            "question": "our (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "My grandparents are happy.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401322.278129,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I miei nonni sono felici.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il loro giardino e' molto grande.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401384.3351486,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Their garden is very big.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "bianco",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401399.7890778,
            "question": "Il tavolo in cucina e' bianc_",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Vostro padre e' intelligente.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401473.479123,
            "question": "Mio padre e' intelligente. (vostro)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401478.3074994,
            "question": "their (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "his/her table",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401454.7556798,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il suo tavolo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "our bed",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401428.198763,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il nostro letto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Le loro camere da letto sono nuove.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401557.3104534,
            "question": "Their bedrooms are new.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il loro tavolo e' verde.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401420.74525,
            "question": "Il mio tavolo e' verde. (loro)",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "miei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401438.8242817,
            "question": "Mio fratello e' intelligente. -> I ___ fratelli sono intelligenti.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "too, also",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401459.3652942,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"anche\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I loro letti sono piccoli.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401585.0217514,
            "question": "Their beds are small.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "simpatiche",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401638.904178,
            "question": "Le studentesse sono simpatich_",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Your father is nice.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401566.486498,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tuo padre e' simpatico.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401631.777121,
            "question": "Il loro apartamento e' grande_",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il nostro tappeto e' nuovo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401621.745349,
            "question": "Il loro tappeto e' nuovo. (nostro)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "sue",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401611.522004,
            "question": "his, her (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "La mia famiglia e' numerosa.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401649.0798876,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My family is big.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "vostra",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453401569.689789,
            "question": "y'alls (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "sue",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453140361.869887,
            "question": "La sua nipote e' di Roma. -> Le ___ nipoti sono di Roma.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "la mia casa",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1453401655.6895714,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"my house\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "La sua camera da letto e' sempre pulita.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453141618.313519,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Her bedroom is always clean.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "instead",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453138922.3009446,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"invece\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "mie",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453141304.302121,
            "question": "my (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "His car is red.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1453226795.2386603,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La sua automobile e' rossa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "her bike",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141808.2995155,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la sua bicicletta\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226519.189058,
            "question": "Il loro divano e' vecchio. -> I ___ divani sono vecchi.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "La tua casa e' piccola.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141797.2394097,
            "question": "La mia casa e' piccola. (tua)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "intelligenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141414.5861483,
            "question": "Le mie cugine sono intelligent_",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tuo padre e' simpatico.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453140586.6983676,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Your father is nice.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My sister, Ann, is very intelligent.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453139378.7765875,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mia sorella, Ann, e' molto intelligente.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "his/her kitchen",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226534.40958,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la sua cucina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "your apartment",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453139391.9769075,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il tuo appartmento\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "nostre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453138671.8729043,
            "question": "La nostra automobile e' rossa. -> Le ___ automobili sono rosse.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Her bike is green.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453139235.8923006,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La sua bicicletta e' verde.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My father, Bob is very nice.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141289.721663,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mio padre, Bob, e' molto simpatico.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "mio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453159305.006243,
            "question": "my (Masculine Singular)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Your sister is intelligent.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141259.200611,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tua sorella e' intelligente.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My family is big.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453140571.4178398,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La mia famiglia e' numerosa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "nostre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453140951.9508893,
            "question": "our (Feminine Plural)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "their rug",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453227414.5795882,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il loro tappeto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My cousins are a little stressed, too.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453225950.489194,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Anche i miei cugini sono un po' stressati.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "tuoi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141084.7551684,
            "question": "your (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "piccola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453142086.8893719,
            "question": "La camera da letto e' piccol_",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "miei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453160258.3411238,
            "question": "my (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Her bedroom is always clean.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453227665.4476726,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La sua camera da letto e' sempre pulita.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "la sua cucina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226553.170456,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"his/her kitchen\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My mother, Laura is a little stressed.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453227358.0779386,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mia madre, Laura, e' un po' stressata.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "mia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226798.1579523,
            "question": "my (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "vostri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453227392.1583464,
            "question": "y'alls (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "my house",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453225998.5109954,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la mia casa\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "very",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226723.8355207,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"molto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Their garden is very big.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141029.0335968,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il loro giardino e' molto grande.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "suoi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453227397.9789283,
            "question": "his, her (Masculine Plural)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "molto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226769.4970863,
            "question": "Given the definition \"very\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mio padre, Bob, e' molto simpatico.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226598.7920177,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"My father, Bob is very nice.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "tuoi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453140121.3018327,
            "question": "Il tuo tavolo e' marrone -> I ___ tavoli sono marroni.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "La vostra cucina e' bella.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141015.8722808,
            "question": "La sua cucina e' bella. (vostra)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il suo letto e' grande.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453139768.1705232,
            "question": "Il mio letto e' grande. (suo)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "loro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453226540.869226,
            "question": "their (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sua",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453139806.7513807,
            "question": "his, her (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "anche",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453160137.4145422,
            "question": "Given the definition \"too, also\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "bianchi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141297.982489,
            "question": "I cuscini sul divano sono bianch_",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "dolce",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453225989.0110457,
            "question": "Mia sorella e' dolc_",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "My garden, on the other hand, is very small.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453141436.5073402,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il mio giardino, invece, e' molto piccolo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tua sorella e' intelligente.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453161272.0510986,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Your sister is intelligent.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "tua",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453161304.8080952,
            "question": "your (Feminine Singular)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Your mom is sweet.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1453159406.0934398,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La tua mamma e' dolce.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}